{
	"questions": [{
		"url": "noimg",
		"Question": "Near a pedestrian crossing, when the pedestrians are waiting to cross the road, you should ",
		"answer1": "Sound horn and proceed ",
		"answer2": "Slow down, sound horn and pass",
		"answer3": "Stop the vehicle and wait till the pedestrians cross the road and then proceed ",
		"correct": "Stop the vehicle and wait till the pedestrians cross the road and then proceed ",
		"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
		"yes": "yes",
		"no": "no"
	},{
		"url": "noimg",
		"Question": "You are approaching a narrow bridge, another vehicle is about to enter the bridge from opposite side you should",
		"answer1": "Increase the speed and try to cross the bridge as fast as possible",
		"answer2": "Put on the head light and pass the bridge",
		"answer3": "Wait till the other vehicle crosses the bridge and then proceed",
		"correct": "Wait till the other vehicle crosses the bridge and then proceed",
		"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
		"yes": "yes",
		"no": "no"
	},{
		"url": "comleftturn",
		"Question": "The following sign represents..",
		"answer1": "Keep left",
		"answer2": "There is no road to the left",
		"answer3": "Compulsory turn left",
		"correct": "Compulsory turn left",
		"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
		"yes": "yes",
		"no": "no"
	},{
		"url": "noimg",
		"Question": "When a vehicle is involved in an accident causing injury to any person",
		"answer1": "Take the vehicle to the nearest police station and report the accident",
		"answer2": "Stop the vehicle and report to the police station",
		"answer3": "Take all reasonable steps to secure medical attention to the injured \n and report to the nearest policestation within 24 hours",
		"correct": "Take all reasonable steps to secure medical attention to the injured \n and report to the nearest policestation within 24 hours",
		"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
		"yes": "yes",
		"no": "no"
	},{
		"url": "giveaway",
		"Question": "The following sign represents...",
		"answer1": "Give way",
		"answer2": "Hospital ahead",
		"answer3": "Traffic island ahead",
		"correct": "Give way",
		"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
		"yes": "yes",
		"no": "no"
	},{
		"url": "noimg",
		"Question": "On a road designated as one way",
		"answer1": "Parking is prohibited",
		"answer2": "Overtaking is prohibited",
		"answer3": "Should not drive in reverse gear",
		"correct": "Should not drive in reverse gear",
		"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
		"yes": "yes",
		"no": "no"
	},{
		"url": "oneway",
		"Question": "The following sign represents..",
		"answer1": "No entry",
		"answer2": "One way",
		"answer3": "Speed limit ends ",
		"correct": "One way",
		"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
		"yes": "yes",
		"no": "no"
	}, {
		"url": "noimg",
		"Question": "You can overtake a vehicle in front",
		"answer1": "Through the right side of that vehicle",
		"answer2": "Through the left side",
		"answer3": "Through the left side, if the road is wide",
		"correct": "Through the right side of that vehicle",
		"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
		"yes": "yes",
		"no": "no"
	},{
		"url": "nouturn",
		"Question": "The following sign represents..",
		"answer1": "Right turn prohibited",
		"answer2": "Sharp curve to the right",
		"answer3": "U-turn prohibited",
		"correct": "U-turn prohibited",
		"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
		"yes": "yes",
		"no": "no"
	},{
		"url": "noimg",
		"Question": "When a vehicle approaches an unguarded railway level crossing, before crossing it, the driver shall",
		"answer1": "Stop the vehicle on the left side of the road, get down from the vehicle, go to the railway track,and\nensure that no train or trolley is coming from either side",
		"answer2": "Sound horn and cross the track as fast as possible",
		"answer3": "Wait till the train passes",
		"correct": "Stop the vehicle on the left side of the road, get down from the vehicle, go to the railway track,and\nensure that no train or trolley is coming from either side",
		"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
		"yes": "yes",
		"no": "no"
	},{
		"url": "pedistriancrossing",
		"Question": "The following sign represents..",
		"answer1": "Pedestrian crossing",
		"answer2": "Pedestrians may enter",
		"answer3": "Pedestrians prohibited",
		"correct": "Pedestrian crossing",
		"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
		"yes": "yes",
		"no": "no"
	},{
		"url": "noimg",
		"Question": "How can you distinguish a transport vehicle.",
		"answer1": "By looking at the tyre size",
		"answer2": "By colour of the vehicle",
		"answer3": "By looking at the number plate of the vehicle",
		"correct": "By looking at the number plate of the vehicle",
		"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
		"yes": "yes",
		"no": "no"
	},{
		"url": "parkrightsideallowed",
		"Question": "The following sign represents..",
		"answer1": "Keep right side",
		"answer2": "Parking on the right allowed",
		"answer3": "Compulsory turn to right",
		"correct": "Parking on the right allowed",
		"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
		"yes": "yes",
		"no": "no"
	},{
		"url": "noimg",
		"Question": "Validity of learners licence ",
		"answer1": "Till the driving licence is obtained",
		"answer2": "6 months",
		"answer3": "30 days",
		"correct": "6 months",
		"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
		"yes": "yes",
		"no": "no"
	},
		{
			"url": "norightturn",
			"Question": "The following sign represents..",
			"answer1": "U- Turn prohibited",
			"answer2": "Right turn prohibited",
			"answer3": "Overtaking through left prohibited",
			"correct": "Right turn prohibited",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},
		{
			"url": "noimg",
			"Question": "In a road without footpath, the pedestrians",
			"answer1": "Should walk on the left side of the road",
			"answer2": "Should walk on the right side of the road",
			"answer3": "May walk on either side of the road",
			"correct": "Should walk on the right side of the road",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},
		{
			"url": "nohorn",
			"Question": "The following sign represents",
			"answer1": "Horn prohibited",
			"answer2": "Compulsory sound horn",
			"answer3": "May sound horn",
			"correct": "Horn prohibited",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},
		{
			"url": "noimg",
			"Question": "Free passage should be given to the following types of vehicles",
			"answer1": "Police vehicles",
			"answer2": "Ambulance and fire service vehicles",
			"answer3": "Express, Super Express buses",
			"correct": "Ambulance and fire service vehicles",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "narrowbridge",
			"Question": "The following sign represents",
			"answer1": "Roads on both sides in front",
			"answer2": "Narrow bridge ahead",
			"answer3": "Narrow road ahead",
			"correct": "Narrow bridge ahead",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "stop",
			"Question": "The following sign represents",
			"answer1": "Stop",
			"answer2": "No parking",
			"answer3": "Hospital ahead",
			"correct": "Stop",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "hospital",
			"Question": "The following sign represents..",
			"answer1": "First aid post",
			"answer2": "Resting place",
			"answer3": "Hospital",
			"correct": "Hospital",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "noimg",
			"Question": "Driver of a vehicle may overtake ?",
			"answer1": "while driving down hill",
			"answer2": "If the road is sufficiently wide",
			"answer3": "When the driver of the vehicle in front shows the signal to overtake",
			"correct": "When the driver of the vehicle in front shows the signal to overtake",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "firstaid",
			"Question": "The following sign represents..",
			"answer1": "First aid post",
			"answer2": "Resting place",
			"answer3": "Hospital",
			"correct": "First aid post",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "noimg",
			"Question": "Driver of a motor vehicle shall drive through",
			"answer1": "The right side of the road",
			"answer2": "The left side of the road",
			"answer3": "The Center of the road",
			"correct": "The left side of the road",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "restplace",
			"Question": "The following sign represents..",
			"answer1": "Hospital",
			"answer2": "Resting place",
			"answer3": "First aid post",
			"correct": "Resting place",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "noimg",
			"Question": "When a Vehicle is parked on the road side during night",
			"answer1": "The vehicle should be locked",
			"answer2": "The person having licence to drive such a vehicle should be in the drivers seat",
			"answer3": "The park light shall remain lit",
			"correct": "The park light shall remain lit",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "endrestriction",
			"Question": "The following sign represents..",
			"answer1": "Road closed",
			"answer2": "No parking",
			"answer3": "End of speed restriction",
			"correct": "End of speed restriction",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "noimg",
			"Question": "Fog lamps are used",
			"answer1": "During night",
			"answer2": "When there is mist",
			"answer3": "When the opposite vehicle is not using dim light",
			"correct": "When there is mist",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "noimg",
			"Question": "The following sign represents..",
			"answer1": "Narrow road ahead",
			"answer2": "Narrow bridge ahead",
			"answer3": "Roads on both sides ahead",
			"correct": "Narrow road ahead",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "noimg",
			"Question": "Zebra lines are meant for..",
			"answer1": "stopping vehicle.",
			"answer2": "pedestrians crossing",
			"answer3": "for giving preference to vehicle",
			"correct": "pedestrians crossing",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "levelcrossingungurded",
			"Question": "The following sign represents..",
			"answer1": "Railway station near",
			"answer2": "Level crossing unguarded",
			"answer3": "Level crossing Guarded",
			"correct": "Level crossing unguarded",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "noimg",
			"Question": "When an ambulance is approaching..",
			"answer1": "allow passage if there are no vehicles from front side",
			"answer2": "no preference need be given",
			"answer3": "the driver shall allow free passage by drawing to the side of the road",
			"correct": "the driver shall allow free passage by drawing to the side of the road",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "noovertake",
			"Question": "The following sign represents..",
			"answer1": "Entry through right side prohibited",
			"answer2": "Entry through left prohibited",
			"answer3": "Overtaking prohibited",
			"correct": "Overtaking prohibited",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "noimg",
			"Question": "Red traffic light indicates..",
			"answer1": "vehicle can proceed with caution",
			"answer2": "stop the vehicle",
			"answer3": "slow down",
			"correct": "stop the vehicle",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "crossroad",
			"Question": "The following sign represents..",
			"answer1": "Cross road",
			"answer2": "No entry",
			"answer3": "Hospital",
			"correct": "Cross road",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "noimg",
			"Question": "Parking a vehicle in front of entrance to hospital",
			"answer1": "Proper",
			"answer2": "Improper",
			"answer3": "Proper if NO PARKING sign is not provided ",
			"correct": "Improper",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "noentry",
			"Question": "The following sign represents..",
			"answer1": "Restriction ends",
			"answer2": "No entry",
			"answer3": "No overtaking",
			"correct": "No entry",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "noimg",
			"Question": "Where the slippery road sign is seen on the road, the driver shall",
			"answer1": "reduce the speed by changing the gear",
			"answer2": "apply brake",
			"answer3": "proceed in the same speed",
			"correct": "reduce the speed by changing the gear",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "sideroadleft",
			"Question": "The following sign represents..",
			"answer1": "May turn to left",
			"answer2": "Compulsory go ahead or turn left",
			"answer3": "Side road left",
			"correct": "Side road left",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "noimg",
			"Question": "Overtaking is prohibited in following circumstances",
			"answer1": "when it is likely to cause inconvenience or danger to other traffic",
			"answer2": "when the vehicle in front is reducing speed",
			"answer3": "during night",
			"correct": "when it is likely to cause inconvenience or danger to other traffic",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "horncompal",
			"Question": "The following sign represents..",
			"answer1": "Sound horn compulsory",
			"answer2": "Sound horn continuously",
			"answer3": "Horn prohibited",
			"correct": "Sound horn compulsory",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "noimg",
			"Question": "Overtaking when approaching a bend",
			"answer1": "is permissible",
			"answer2": "not permissible",
			"answer3": "is permissible with care",
			"correct": "not permissible",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "comturnright",
			"Question": "The following sign represents..",
			"answer1": "Road to the right in front",
			"answer2": "Compulsory turn right",
			"answer3": "Turn to right prohibited",
			"correct": "Compulsory turn right",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "noimg",
			"Question": "Drunken driving",
			"answer1": "allowed in private vehicles",
			"answer2": "allowed during night time",
			"answer3": "prohibited in all vehicles",
			"correct": "prohibited in all vehicles",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "nopark",
			"Question": "The following sign represents..",
			"answer1": "End of restriction",
			"answer2": "Do not stop",
			"answer3": "No parking",
			"correct": "No parking",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "noimg",
			"Question": "Use of horn prohibited",
			"answer1": "Mosque, Church and Temple",
			"answer2": "Near Hospital, Courts of Law",
			"answer3": "Near Police Station",
			"correct": "Near Hospital, Courts of Law",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "oneway",
			"Question": "The sign represents",
			"answer1": "Go straight",
			"answer2": "One-way",
			"answer3": "Prohibited in both direction",
			"correct": "One-way",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "noimg",
			"Question": "Rear view mirror is used",
			"answer1": "for seeing face",
			"answer2": "for watching the traffic approaching from behind",
			"answer3": "for seeing the back seat passenger",
			"correct": "for watching the traffic approaching from behind",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
			"url": "noimg",
			"Question": "Vehicles proceeding from opposite direction should be allowed to pass through",
			"answer1": "Your right side",
			"answer2": "Your left side",
			"answer3": "The convenient side",
			"correct": "Your right side",
			"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
			"yes": "yes",
			"no": "no"
		},{
		"url": "noimg",
		"Question": "The sign represents ",
		"answer1": "No entry for motor vehicles",
		"answer2": "No entry for cars and motor cycles",
		"answer3": "Entry allowed for cars and motor vehicles",
		"correct": "No entry for motor vehicles",
		"messege": "Do you want to close the exam?",
		"yes": "yes",
		"no": "no"
	}]
}